Polisar, Eric Papers /3035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILR course materials; correspondence; committee meetings and other misc. (Box 8)
  - ILR 508 - Preparation of Labor Relations, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - ILR 601, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - ILR 602, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Spring
  - Business Studies - N. Texas State University, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - NYS School Boards Association Inc. Research Bulletin, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - University of Maryland Program, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Information files: ACW, disarmament, steward training, grievance procedure, foreign trade, civil rights (Box 9)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers - Disarmament, 1958-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Includes: Statistics, and hand written accounts
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers - Disarmament, 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Includes: Statistics
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers - Disarmament, 1947-1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Includes: Research Dept. Statistics, and Men's Wear article/newspaper
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers - Disarmament, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Includes mostly statistics from the research dept. and a newspaper
  - Mobilization for Peace: Civilian Diversification of Airframe Industry, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Chapters I - V
  - Mobilization for Peace: Civilian Diversification of Airframe Industry, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Chapters VI - XII. Includes a magazine article
  - The Economy, Politics, and Disarmament, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Includes: booklets/pamphlets
  - Steward Training Grievance Procedure, 1951-1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Trade, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Information files: automation, NY-Industry (Erie-Niagara area) Collective Bargaining, Public Employee and the Right to Strike, Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of NYS Commission for Human Rights. (Box 10)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Northeast Staff Institute, ILGWU. April
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1959-1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Includes: newspaper
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1956-1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Automation, 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Automation, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - N.Y. Industry (Erie-Niagara Area), 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - N.Y. Industry (Erie-Niagara Area), 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - N.Y. Industry (Erie-Niagara Area), 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Includes: Magazine
  - Collective Bargaining, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Includes: Newspapers magazines, and articles
  - Public Employees and the Right to Strike, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Public Employees and the Right to Strike, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Public Employees and the Right to Strike, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Law and Equal Employment, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Riots and the Law or Who Enforces which Law against whom?, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Contract between NYC and Welfare Local 271, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Includes multiple contract booklets from June 1965
- Mss.: Public employees and the Right to Strike; The Law and Equal Employment; Riots and the Law; Staff Report (Box 11)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in EmploymentOperation of the NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rules of the Public Employment Relations Board (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Root Causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Root causes of Public Employee Bargaining: An Overview, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - NYS 4639 In Senate - Public Employee's Fair Employment Act, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- ILR Course material; AFL-CIO Convention and other reports; AFSCME information (Box 12)
  - ILR Evaluations, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ILR Courses, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Includes: Evaluations, collective bargaining notes, social problems of industrialization, and course roster
  - ILR 300 - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ILR 300 - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes: Exams, syllabus, collective bargaining
  - ILR 402 - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - ILR 402, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Includes: Course registration cards, questionnaires, and rosters
  - ILR 402 - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Includes: Reports and Contracts
  - ILR 402 - Students' Term Papers, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ILR 402 - Students' Term Papers, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - ILR 402 - Students' Term Papers, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ILR 402 - Students' Term Papers, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Includes: Bulletins and articles
  - AFL-CIO Per Capita Surveys, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Includes: Salaries, dues, taxes, and membership information
  - Statement by George Meany, President, AFL, and CIO, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Platform Proposals of the AFL-CIO National Convention, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Structure of the AFL-CIO (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Annual Convention, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - AFL-CIO Western Pulp and Paper Workers (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - AFL-CIO Apprenticeship Training, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Buffalo AFL-CIO Council, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - AFL-CIO - Public Employees - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA), 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Includes: Articles and pamphlets
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ACWA - The Advance Newspaper, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ACWA - Readings on "Power in American Society" (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - ACWA - The Advance Newspaper, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME - General Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - AFSCME Staff Intern Program, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - AFSCME Constitution Revision, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - AFSCME Union Recognition Manual, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- AFSCME Material; building trades files; union files; IAM, IUD, IBEW, IUE, Meat Cutters, National Maritime Union (Box 13)
  - AFSCME Proposed Constitution, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME Proposed Constitution, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - First Draft of AFSCME Constitution, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME Constitutional Revision Commission, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Contact info: Names and phone numbers
  - Milwaukee Constitution Expenses, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - NYC AFSCME Constitution Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis AFSCME Constitution Expenses, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles AFSCME Constitution Expenses, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Minneapolis AFSCME Constitution Expenses and Convention, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Chicago AFSME Constitution Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Washington D.C. AFSCME Constitution Expenses, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME Staff Discussion Session, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Other AFSCME Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME -Miscellaneous Materials, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Includes: Maps and charts
  - Union Constitutions, Affairs, Reports, etc. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Include: pamphlets
  - AFSCME Committee to Examine Collective Bargaining, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Program Request - "Union Administration" - American Newspaper Guild, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Building Trades Employers Association - Wage Rate Schedule, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Building Industry and Builders Exchange, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Building Industry and Builders Exchange, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bulletins, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Builders Exchange News Letter, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Builders Exchange Council of Auburn, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Builders Exchange-Elmira, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - "Money May Talk", 1964 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Pittsburgh Rail Rates, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo Industrial Progress Council, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mayor's Statement to Buffalo Industrial Progress Council (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - American Federation of Grain Millers-Buffalo, 1950-1963 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Includes: an article
  - Niagara Mohawk Rate Proceeding, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Document from 1959 but forwarded in 1968
  - Hotel Statistical Data and General Information, 1948-1964 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - IAM - Machinists Leadership Schools - 75th Year, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    IAM - International Association of Machinists
  - ILR- Contracts, Forms, Cases, Worksheets, Etc., 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - IVEW, Labor History, Conferences -Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - IBEW Course, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - IUD Buildings and Agenda, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Includes: Magazines and Articles
  - IUE- Leadership Training Institute - Rutgers, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Research Project- Mack Truck Dunellen, N.J., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Manhattan Bronx Postal Union, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    Includes: Articles
  - National Maritime Union, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Includes general office files and union related files of SIU, SSEU, IBT, UPP, UPWA, UAW; and civil rights material (Box 14)
  - NYC Welfare, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - SIU-Parliamentary Debates, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    SIU - Seafarer's International Union
  - Social Service Employee Union, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Teamster's Union, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Studies Center - "The Stimulated Union", 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Statler - Staff Programs. Agenda, and Questionnaire, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Questionnaire, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - TOP Advisory Council (White Collar Conference), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    TOP- Technical, Office, and Professional Dept.
  - Automation, Technology, and Jobs - The American Labor Movement, Union Cause, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - UAW- Syracuse- Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - News from UAW, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Extension Program: Postal Employee Training, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Executive Order 10988, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Grievance Procedure and Federal News Service, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - UPP - Economic Report, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    UPP-United Papermakers and Paperworkers
  - United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers (UPWA) - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The Need for Relevance in Labor Education, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - News Articles, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - United Rubber Workers of America - Educational Conference, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Pamphlets of United Rubber Workers(URW), 1956-1960 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - CURW - East Harlem Project, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    CURW-Cornell United Religious Work
  - CURW - East Harlem Project, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Reports and Evaluations
  - A. Phillip Randolph Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - NAACP - McComb, MI Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Race and Discrimination, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Course Outline
  - NAACP Convention - Requests, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Coahoma County NAACP Branch, "Cryer", 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Includes: News Articles
  - Pamphlet, "Equal Rights for All" (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - News from the AFL-CIO, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - East Lansing, Michigan, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Milwaukee Urban League, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous- National Urban League, Michigan, Development and Employment, and the Probe, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Includes: Newspaper about the "New African American" and a Maps of Michigan
  - NY Urban League Youth Employment Center - Progress Report, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Poverty Rights Action Center, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - NY County Lawyers Association Committee on Civil Rights, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Racial Tensions In NYS - Committee on Law Reform, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - NYC Commission on Human Rights, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Minister's Committee on Job Opportunities For Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- CU, NYSSILR Workshop on discrimination in employment; other civil rights committee information, Local 28 case, etc. (Box 15)
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    NAACP Convention
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ILR-Workshop On Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - City Commission on Human Rights, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Racial Bias in the Building Industry - Report to Mayor, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - UCLA - National Urban League, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - NYS Joint Legislation Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NYS Joint Legislation Committee - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Memos to File - Joint Legislation Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination in Employment - Staff Report to JLC, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    JLC- Joint Legislation Committee
  - JLC - Correspondence Re: Staff Report, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin on Discrimination and Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Memos to File
  - Outline and Corrections on Discrimination Report, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Draft 1 and Part 2 - Discrimination in Employment, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Periodicals, Bulletins, Vouchers, and JLC, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Miscellaneous
  - NYS Advisory Committee to US Commission on Civil Rights, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Newsletter, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - City of Poughkeepsie on Human Relations Report, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Report - Building Industry of NYC Referral Committee, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Memos to Files: State Commission for Human Rights (SCHR), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reports - NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Includes: A data table of statistics starting from 1945
  - State Commission for Human Rights - Budgets, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - SCHR- Law Against Discrimination, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - JLC-Discrimination, SCHR, and Local 28 Case, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Local 28 Case, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - SCHR- Iron Workers Case, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - SCHR Case - Plumbers Union 373 - R AND S Plumbing, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - SCHR Case- Bank vs. Capital Airlines Hearings, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Documents that reference 1960
  - SCHR Case - Sol Waxman vs. Pic Design Corp., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - SCHR Cases - Sol Waxman vs. Pic Design Corp., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - SCHR Cases - Sol Waxman vs. Pic Design Corp., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Includes ILR course material, civil rights files (Box 16)
  - Buffalo Construction Industry - Investigation Report, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Special Labor Force Reports, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Includes: Labor Force projections by color/race 1970-1980
  - NAACP -Workshop on Discrimination in Employment, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Attitudes Toward Desegregation by Herbert Hyman and Paul Sheatsley, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    This is a document of interest give to Eric Polisar in 1965
  - Antidiscrimination Laws In Action - Rutgers Law Review (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lopez - Current Problems in Test Performance of Job Applicants, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ray Marshall's Paper on EEO and Discussion, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    EEO: Equal Employment Opportunity
  - Bayard Rustin - Watts "Manifesto" and McCone Report, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    (Article)
  - The Negro Family and Commentary, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Commentary by Daniel P. Moynihan
  - NCCJ - Merit Employment is Good Business, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    NCCJ- National Conference of Christians and Jews
  - Tom Kahn - The Economics of Equality, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Sheppard and Striner - Civil Rights, Employment, and the Social Status of American Negroes, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Civil Service Commission Reports - Minority Employment on the Rise, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Joe Russell - Changing Patterns of Non-White Workers, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Felician Foltman - National and State Apprenticeship, 1960-1966 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Stanley Young - Manpower Training Some Cost Dimensions (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bullock - Poverty in the Ghetto and L.A., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Plan for Progress - Company/American Business Material, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Special Census of Monroe County, NY, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Fair Employment Practice Commission (FEPC), 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    California Documents
  - Fair Employment Practice Commission Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Illinois Documents
  - Memphis Tennessee Sanitation Strike, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Michigan - Report of Progress, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Division on Civil Rights, 1961-1967 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Includes: articles, posters, and pamphlets
  - N.J. Division on Civil Rights Case - Thomas Peyton Sellers v. Philips Barber Shop, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Pennsylvania Human Relations Commission, 1963-1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania and Philadelphia Human Relations Commissions, 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Civil Rights Commission, 1960-1967 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Ohio Civil Rights Commission, 1960-1967 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Memphis Agreement, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - ILR 250 - Spring, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Includes: Class cards, student grades, course descriptions, etc.
  - ILR 300 -Class Notes, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - ILR 300, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Includes: Class schedule/syllabus, roster, and final exam
- Government statistics on the labor market and minorities, other civil rights material (Box 17)
  - Equality of Educational Opportunity - Report, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Appendix to the Survey on Equality of Educational Opportunity, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mayhew - Massachusetts Anti-Discrimination Law, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Prentice Hall Inc.- New Civil Rights Law and Your Business, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Wayne University - Patterns of Discrimination in Employment, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Employment Distribution Study of Construction Industry in Michigan, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NYS Commission for Human Rights, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NYS Commission for Human Rights Investigation Report (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - NYS Commission for Human Rights - Report of Progress, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - NYS Industrial Bulletin, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Reports, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Convocation: The Urban Coalition, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Equality of Educational Opportunity, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - US Commission on Civil Rights - Racial Isolation in Public Schools, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - US Commission on Civil Rights - Racial Isolation in Public Schools, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO Civil Rights Materials, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Quarterly(CQ) - Revolution in Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Notes on May-June Rioting, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Herbert Hill - Demographic Change and Racial Ghettos: The Crisis of American Cities, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Herbert Hill - Racial Inequality in Employment: The Patterns of Discrimination, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Herbert Hill - Sewing Machines and Union Machines, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Article
  - The Role of Law in Securing Equal Employment Opportunity: Legal Powers and Social Change, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Written By Herbert Hill
  - Labor Secretary, Herbert Hill's Testimony NAACP, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - National Urban League, Inc. - Labor Union Project, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment In Metropolitan Washington, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - EEOC: Office of Liaison, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    EEOC: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission
  - State/Local Fair Employment Practice Agencies, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - US Dept. of Labor - Summary Of State FEP Acts, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    FEP: Fair Employment Practice
  - Negro Women: In Population and Labor Force, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Occupational Outlook - The Negro's Occupational Progress, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - The Negro Journey to the City, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Changing Patterns in Employment of Non-White workers, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - A century of Change: Negroes in the U.S. Economy, 1860-1960, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Special Labor Report No. 53, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    U.S. Dept. of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Major Bureau of Labor Statistic Programs, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Poverty Areas of Major Cities, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    Special Labor Force No.75
  - BLS - Changing Patterns of Work and Workers in Urban Environments, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    BLS: Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - BLS - Employment of High School Graduates and Dropouts in 1964, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Bienstock - The Fact of Poverty in NYC, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Bienstock - Job Market Realities for the High School Dropout, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - A " Freedom Budget" for ALL Americans, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Arthur Rose Speech - Social Statistics and Social Policy: 3 Views of Man, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Andrew Brimmer - Economic Progress in Black and White, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 44)